http://www.gsccc.org/en/our-council/about-our-council/privacy-policy.html

MY GS
JOIN ABOUT OUR COUNCILAbout Our CouncilKeeping Our Girl Scout Community SafeBoard of DirectorsCommunity PartnersEmploymentForms and DocumentsLocations and FacilitiesNewsShopContact UsStaff DirectoryThe BridgePublications EVENTS COOKIES+ VOLUNTEER CAMP DONATE MY GS
COVID-19 Response
eBiz
Join
Shop
Forms
Blog
Contact Us
About Our CouncilKeeping Our Girl Scout Community SafeBoard of DirectorsCommunity PartnersEmploymentForms and DocumentsLocations and FacilitiesNewsShopContact UsStaff DirectoryThe BridgePublications
Our Council
About Our CouncilPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Web site is owned by Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast, a
501(c)(3) non-profit organization headquartered in Chesapeake, VA. Our
online properties comprise of, but are not limited to, all pages found
under www.gsccc.org. This Privacy Policy applies to these sites and
other sites, mobile apps or other online services we operate that link
to this policy (collectively, referred to below as the site).
Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast is committed to respecting and
protecting the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy discloses
how we collect, protect, and use information you provide or we collect
online, as well as how we protect children's privacy. If our policy
practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting our
revised Privacy Policy on our site, with a date of revision included
below. By using the pages on this site or other services covered by
the posted Privacy Policy, you are accepting the practices described
in the Privacy Policy. Please review this Privacy Policy frequently.
INFORMATION COLLECTION
Personally Identifiable Information
At our site, we do not collect personally identifiable information
from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and
knowingly. This means we do not require you to register or provide
information to us in order to view our site. Girl Scouts of the
Colonial Coast only gathers personally identifiable data, such as
names, addresses, Zip/postal codes, e-mail addresses, etc., when
voluntarily submitted by a visitor. Once collected, we may combine
this information with other information collected from external sources.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast may automatically collect certain
technical information from your computer such as your Internet service
provider, your Internet Protocol address, your browser type, your
operating system, the pages viewed, the pages viewed immediately
before and after accessing the Web site, and the search terms entered
to get to our site. This information allows us to improve and
customize our services. We and our service providers may collect this
information using “cookies,” which are small text files that many
websites save on your computer, or similar technologies. See the
section on “Use of Cookies and Similar Technology” below for more information.
USE AND SHARING OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
The personally identifiable information you provide is used by Girl
Scouts of Colonial Coast and other entities who are involved in the
operation of this site or who provide support for the Girl Scouts of
the Colonial Coast and Girl Scouts of the USA mission and programs,
for general business purposes and for the purposes for which you
provided the information.  General business purposes include, for
example, Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast and Girl Scouts of the USA
membership activities, program participation, marketing, promotions,
and fundraising activities and communications.  The purposes, for
which you provide information includes our use of your personally
identifiable information to process online transactions, purchases,
and donations, facilitate participation in Girl Scouts of the USA and
Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast programs, promotions and services,
or process job applications. We do not sell information you provide to
us online to third parties. We may share personally identifiable
information with third parties when (i) with other Girl Scout Councils
and Girl Scout troops for administrative purposes relating to a
child’s activities with another Council or their troop; (ii) when the
person submitting the information authorizes us to share it; (iii)
when sharing the information is a necessary operation of the site, for
instance, to process a credit card donation, purchase or other
transaction you may choose to make; (iv) to facilitate participation
in Girl Scouts of the USA and Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast
programs, promotions, and services, or to engage in fund raising,
marketing communications and promotions; (v) to comply with legal
processes such as a subpoena or court order or to otherwise protect
your or our legal rights; or (vi) for other purposes for which you
provided the information. Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast has no
control over or responsibility for the data collection and use
practices of third parties that process online transactions.  For
example, if you make a donation or purchase on our site using a credit
card or online payment account or similar account of a third party
payment provider, certain information is transmitted to the payment
provider and is subject to the third party’s own privacy policy.
Note that Girl Scouts of the USA provides operational support for
the site and may collect and use personally identifiable information
you provide to the site and other information collected by the site as
described in this policy. In addition, the “shop” links on our site
take you to a shopping page that is hosted or controlled by Girl
Scouts of the USA, and not by Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast.
Girl Scouts of the USA will use any information it collects in
accordance with its own privacy policy, which is available here.
Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast and Girl Scouts of the USA are each
responsible for their own information handling practices.
CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast is committed to providing a safe,
secure, and fun online experience for children who visit our site. We
are dedicated to safeguarding any personal information collected
online and to helping parents and children have positive experiences
on the Internet.
We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information
from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental
consent. With parental consent, we may collect information from
children under the age of 13 such as: name, address, email address,
account information, and user generated content. This information
allows us to fulfill a requested transaction and facilitate
participation in online programs, keep records, undertake certain
marketing activities, or to otherwise customize or enhance the Web
site experience for children.
Children under the age of 13 may be able to make certain content
such as user generated content visible to others or the public. This
could include, for example, a webpage or parts of webpages operated by
children that have been designed for group or public viewing. However,
absent parental consent, children under 13 would be allowed to display
only limited information such as a first name or unique user name or
other information that does not allow for online contacting by third parties.
Regardless of what information is displayed, parents can revoke
their consent and ask that information about their children be deleted
from the site by contacting our offices by phone at 1-800-777-2688. To
do this or to review personal information collected from children, we
must verify the identity of the requesting parent. When a parent
revokes consent, we will stop collecting, using, or disclosing
information from that child. To respect the privacy of parents,
information collected and used for the sole purpose of obtaining
verifiable parental consent or providing notice is not maintained in
retrievable form by the site if parental consent is not obtained after
a reasonable time.
Submissions
Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast welcomes children to learn more
about our organization and, where appropriate, participate in polls
and surveys, as well as submit comments, artwork, writings, and other
submissions for posting on our Web site. For this reason, Girl Scouts
of the Colonial Coast follows the guidelines for interactive
electronic media published by the Children's Advertising Review Unit
(CARU) of the Better Business Bureau for pages targeted to children
under 13. However, we encourage this be done only with their parent's
knowledge and supervision. We also encourage children to use an alias,
first name, nickname, initials, or other alternative to full names or
screen names which correspond with an e-mail address for any
activities which will involve public posting.
In keeping with CARU's Principle regarding respecting and fostering
the parents' role in providing guidance for their children, we
encourage parents to check and monitor their children's use of e-mail
and other online activities regularly.
USE OF COOKIES AND SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES
Visitors should be aware that non-personal information and data
might be automatically collected by the Girl Scouts of the Colonial
Coast website through the use of "cookies" or other similar
technologies such as web beacons. "Cookies" are small text
files a Web site can use to recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the
visitor's ongoing access to and use of the site, and allow a site to
track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow
content improvements. Cookies are not programs that come onto a
visitor's system and damage files.
Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor
that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a visitor does not
want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a
simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or
accept the cookie feature. “Web beacons” are a small snippet of code
embedded in
webpages typically used to monitor activity on a webpage and transfer
or collect information, such as information about your Internet
Protocol address, the URL of the page on which the beacon is located,
the browser type that is accessing the site, and the ID number of
cookies placed on your computer.
Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast uses "cookie" technology
only to obtain non-personal information from its online visitors in
order to improve visitors' online experience and facilitate their
visit within our site. Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast may use web
beacons to improve website services, conduct website analytics, first
party advertising relating to us, and our sponsors, and to optimize
the browsing experience.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit
our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable
information (that is, not including your name, address, e-mail
address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web
sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of
interest to you on this or other websites. Read more information about
this practice at http://www.networkadvertising.org/
and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/
to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES
This site may be linked to other sites and services that are not
maintained by Girl Scouts of the Colonial Coast. These Web sites have
their own privacy policies, which you should review prior to visiting
them. We have no responsibility for linked Web sites and provide these
links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
OUR SECURITY SAFEGUARD
The safety and security of your online experience is of the utmost
concern to us. We take measures to implement reasonable physical,
electronic, and managerial procedures are in place to safeguard and
help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and
correctly use the information we collect online.
Credit Card Safety
Protecting the safety of your credit card information is important
to us.  For card transactions we process, we use Secure Sockets Layer
(SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit card
information as it is transmitted to us. SSL is the industry standard
in Internet encryption technology and a method of scrambling data as
it travels from your computer to our Web site servers. We also encrypt
your credit card number when we store your order and whenever we
transfer that information to participating merchants.
To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit
sensitive information, check the document for your browser for
indication of an SSL connection (most browsers utilize an unbroken or
closed padlock). Verify that SSL is active before submitting sensitive
information to our server. To double-check, verify that the URL or
Address line of your browser for our site begins with "https."
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to
your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished
using a shared computer.
Children
If you are under 18, you need parent/guardian permission to use a
credit card to make purchases online.
HOW TO CONTACT US
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact
us at:
You can contact us via email at mailto:customercare@gsccc.org.
Send us your question and we will get back to you as soon as possible.
Thank you for visiting our site.
This Privacy Policy was last updated in September 2016.
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
Volunteer Connection
